bstrustseal.com 2014-06-15

# Bayshore Free Trust Certificate - Gain trust amoung your visitors and increase your sale

**About us**

This privacy policy applies to the websites operated by Bayshore ("Bayshore", "we", "our" and "us") and to the processing of personal information by Bayshore as contemplated in this privacy policy. Any reference to "you" or "your" means you, the user. 

Bayshore respects your privacy and is committed to protecting the personal information you share with us. This statement describes how we collect and use your personal information that we may collect about you through the Sites and from our communications with you. The Sites are hosted on various servers within the European Economic Area. 

**Data Protection Laws**

We are conscious of our legal responsibilities as a "data controller" and we support the principles of data protection reflected in the 1995 EU Directive on Data Protection and applicable national implementing legislation. We shall endeavour to ensure that the personal information we obtain and use will always be held, used, transferred and otherwise processed in accordance with our legal obligations. 

**Other websites**  
There may be links from the Sites to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to the Sites and not to any other websites including any websites linked from any of the Sites. Acc  
essing those third party websites or sources requires you to leave the Sites. We do not control those third party websites or any of the content they contain and you expressly acknowledge and agree that we are in no way responsible or liable for any of those third party websites, including, without limitation, the content, policies, failures, promotions, products, services or actions of those websites and/or any damages, losses, failures or problems caused by, related to or arising from those websites. We encourage you to review all policies, rules, terms and regulations, including the privacy policies, of each website that you visit.  
How we obtain personal information about you

We may as a result of your interaction with our Sites and our communications with you hold and process personal information obtained about you. The types of personal information we collect may include:

• your name  
• your phone number  
• your email address  
• your address  
• your credit card information  
• your date of birth  

**How we collect and use non-personal information**

Please note that when anyone visits any of the Sites, we automatically collect certain non-personal information such as the type of computer operating system (e.g., Windows or Mac OS) and browser (e.g., Safari, Netscape, Internet Explorer) being used, and the domain name of the internet service provider. We sometimes use the non-personal information that we collect to improve the design and content of the Sites and to enable us to personalise your experience. 

What we do with your personal information  
The personal information that you provide will be available to Ideal Standard, our affiliated companies and trusted third party service providers and contractors for the following purposes:

• to process enquiries received via the Sites  
• to register you for and send you newsletters  
• to conduct market research and business development   
• to provide you with information about products and promotions that may be of interest to you from ourselves   
• in connection with surveys related to our products and the Sites  
• any other purpose indicated at the time you voluntarily provide your personal information 

**Marketing**

We may from time to time use your personal information to send you automated email messages or marketing materials regarding our services and the services of third party suppliers, in each case with your prior consent. These email messages may contain features that help us make sure you received and were able to open the message. 

You may opt out of receiving such marketing email messages at any time, free of charge, by replying to the message with "unsubscribe" in the subject line, or by following the instructions in any marketing communication.

**Disclosing your personal information**

We will never disclose your personal information to companies and individuals who perform business functions and services on our behalf. 

We may disclose your personal information if, in our opinion, disclosure is required by law.

**Cookies and tracking software**

What is in a cookie?

A cookie is a simple text file that is stored on your computer or mobile device by a website's server and only that server will be able to retrieve or read the contents of that cookie. Each cookie is unique to your web browser. It will contain some anonymous information such as a unique identifier and the site name and some digits and numbers. It allows a website to remember things like your preferences or what's in your shopping basket

How do we use cookies?

We use "cookies" and other types of tracking software in order to personalise your visit to our Sites and enhance your experience by gaining a better understanding of your particular interests and customising our pages for you. 

We may use the information provided by cookies to analyse trends, administer the Sites, or for research and marketing purposes to help us better serve you. No information which personally identifies you will be collected through the cookies.

Our Sites require the use of cookies in order to work at their best. If you do not wish these cookies to be used then please note that you may not experience our Sites working to their best effect.

**The accuracy of your information**

While we endeavour to ensure that the information we hold about you is acc  
urate and kept up to date, we shall assume that in the absence of evidence to the contrary, the information you provide us with is accurate. Should you inform us of inaccuracies in the information which we hold in relation to you or, if we discover that such information is inaccurate, it shall be promptly rectified by us. We do not intentionally retain any information about you which is out of date or which is no longer required.

**Personal Data Security and Confidentiality**

We maintain adequate technical and organisational security measures to protect your personal information from loss, misuse, and unauthorised acc  
ess, disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

**Access and Correction Rights**

You can request access to, and have the opportunity to update and amend your personal information by by clicking on the "Profile Update" button in the Member's Area and completing the relevant information. and you can exercise any other rights you enjoy under applicable data protection laws, including, for example, objection to and blocking of the processing of your personal information, by contacting us at webmaster@bayshoreweb.com. For security reasons, we reserve the right to take steps to authenticate your identity before providing access to your personal information.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us via email.
